pokemon-revolution-online.net 2018-12-26

# Pokemon Revolution Online - Privacy Policy

Your personal information and privacy are important to Pokémon Revolution Online (PRO). Establishing and maintaining a trusting relationship between our service and our players is crucial to the success of this game, and this Privacy Policy has been created and enforced with the intent of allowing our users to feel comfortable and safe while participating in our services.

If you feel that PRO are not abiding by its posted policies, you should contact an Administrator via the PRO Team Page.

Personal Information is information that someone would be able to use to contact or identify you. This includes information such as your full name, telephone number, or email address. Personal Information does not include compiled data that by itself cannot be used to identify an individual person (such as the percentage of users that hail from a specific country).

This Privacy Policy is a part of our End-User License Agreement and Terms of Service Agreements, and by participating in any portion of the service you agree to be bound by its terms and conditions. This Privacy Policy only addresses activities conducted within our services. Any other website or service (including those to which we may link) may have their own policies, which we do not control, and thus are not addressed, controlled, or influenced by this policy.

I Collection of Personal Information You provide certain Personal Information, such as your email address, upon registering with the PRO service, sending support emails to PRO, and via completion of forms or other questionnaires sent to us.

II How Personal Information May be Used Any Personal Information submitted to PRO may be used by PRO for a variety of reasons, within reasonable limitation.

This information may be used to identify rightful possession of an account in the event of a lost or stolen password. This information may be used to identify multiple accounts as falling under the possession of one individual. This information may be used to prevent those in possession of terminated accounts future access to the service. This information may be used to provide optional email updates from either our website or forums, at the sole discretion of you, the user. This information may be used to verify the status of a donation made to PRO.

In the highly unlikely event that legal authorities request PRO to provide such Personal Information for use in any legal context, PRO will be required to oblige the requests of such authorities.

This information may not and will not be shared with any third party source, with the exception of law enforcement officials as previously noted. This information may not and will not be sold to any third party source. This information may not and will not be gathered unwillingly or without the knowledge of its provider under any circumstance; all information collected by PRO must be consented by its source.

III Child Protection In order to protect the privacy interests of minors, we do not allow children under the age of 18 to participate in any service provided by PRO, including forums and game, without the consent of a parent or guardian.

IV Accessing an Account PRO staff may be required to access your account. This access is required for our services to identify any errors and monitor suspicious activity.

For the game, staff may be required to monitor your activity. Private messages cannot be viewed and your password will not be required. Staff will never ask you for your password.

V Protection of Personal Information PRO takes necessary precautions to protect our users information; any information willingly provided to PRO is protected both online and offline.

We have established and maintain reasonable security procedures to protect the confidentiality and integrity of your Personal Information. Encryption and other security measures (such as but not limited to off-site backup and password protection), as well as any combination of such practices, are used by PRO to help provide our users with adequate security in regards to private data.

The number of individuals who have access to any Personal Information collected by PRO is limited to a very small number of people, and our staff is routinely updated and debriefed as our security practices develop and evolve. Staff will be limited in the type of Personal Information they can access depending on the access level the staff member has.

By participating in any portion of any service provided by PRO, including forums and game, you acknowledge that "perfect security" does not exist on the internet and that PRO will execute to the fullest extent of their power the best security and protection possible to ensure the integrity of your Personal Information.
